(Sheldon:)Sorry, I have company.
(Raj:)Come on, Sheldon, open the door.
(Sheldon:)I don't want to hug you.
(Sheldon:)I don't want to
hug you, either.
(Raj:)I was just
feeling blue.
(Sheldon:)Blue, as in depressed.
(Raj:)Well, not so much
depressed as lonely.
(Sheldon:)I don't know what
color lonely is.
(Leonard:)- What?
- Red is angry;
yellow is frightened;
green is jealous;
and blue is depressed.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps we can assign
a color to lonely.
(Raj:)Nothing rhymes with orange.
It's probably lonely.
(Sheldon:)All right. Come in.
(Sheldon:)You look positively
orange with loneliness.
(Sheldon:)No, I don't see that
catching on at all.
(Raj:)What are you doing?
(Sheldon:)I'm working on my
three-person chess game.
(Raj:)Oh, cool. Can I play?
(Sheldon:)It's three-person chess.